planbook.com 2017-12-14

# Planbook.com Privacy Policy

Planbook.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.

**What personally identifiable information does planbook.com collect from me?**

Planbook.com believes that as little personal information as possible should be collected from our users. The personal information we collect for planbook.com is contained on the User Settings page, and the only required item is your email address. 

In addition to the information we collect on the User Settings page, we may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you contact our support team. Furthermore, when you send e-mail or other communication to planbook.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

**What are cookies and how does planbook.com use them?**

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, planbook.com may use cookies to temporarily store information about you. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. We may use cookies to better display our website, to save you time, and to provide better technical support. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some planbook.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**How does planbook.com use my information?**

Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our site and a high level of user support. 

Planbook.com does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, from our server log files, or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve our users; for instance, this information often gives us ideas for improving our products. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. 

**Who is collecting information?**

When you are on planbook.com and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with planbook.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected or maintained by any company other than planbook.com, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer.

**With whom does planbook.com share my information?**

As a general rule, planbook.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the reasons that your information may be disclosed.

Business Partners and Sponsors. Planbook.com will never disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, unless it is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. If planbook.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Third Party Data and Data in the Aggregate. Under confidentiality agreements, planbook.com may match user information with third party data. Also, planbook.com discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 8% of our users are from Illinois) in order to describe our services to current and prospective partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

Other. planbook.com may release personal information if it has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property, or safety of planbook.com, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

**What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?**

Planbook.com may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services. Only planbook.com will send you these direct mailings.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. However, if you choose to reject all cookies you may be unable to use select planbook.com services.

Planbook.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service. 

**What is the planbook.com policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?**

You may edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the Settings link. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

If you have forgotten your password, click the Forgot password link on the login screen. Enter your email address, and if the email address matches our records your password will be sent to this email address. For all other problems logging into Planbook services, please contact Planbook support at support@planbook.com.

Please contact us at support@planbook.com for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your planbook.com account. Residual information will remain within our archive records.

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

Your account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this information. You may edit your planbook.com personal information at any time by clicking on the Settings link.

If you have forgotten your password, click the Forgot password link on the login screen. Enter your email address, and if the email address matches our records your password will be sent to this email address. For all other problems logging into Planbook services, please contact Planbook support at support@planbook.com.

For your protection, remember to sign out of planbook.com before closing your browser. You can sign out by clicking the Sign out link. After signing out, make sure to close your browser window. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a public computer.

We restrict access to personal information to planbook.com employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**What about children's privacy?**

Planbook.com accounts are intended for individuals, age 18 and over, who function in the role of an educator. Account holders may allow their students of all ages to view information online, but at no time does planbook.com collect information from these students, or any other individuals who view the information shared by their educator. 

Planbook.com does not gather information on the ages of our users and will never knowingly share personally identifying information about users who are under the age of 18 with business partners or other third parties. When contacting our users, planbook.com requests that anyone under the age of 18 forward the e-mail to a parent or guardian. All planbook.com account holders, including parents and children with planbook.com accounts, are subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Additional Information**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your personal information by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

If you have a question regarding this statement, or if a question was not addressed in this privacy policy, you may contact us at support@planbook.com. We will do our best to answer your question promptly and accurately.
